all right I realized yesterday at like
11 p.m. that I had forgotten to do my
video for the day
and I was not gonna do it then and
there's a piece of me that when I fail
like that when I've made a commitment to
do something for 90 days or 10 days as
soon as I don't do it it all falls apart
and how perfect that the audio and video
doesn't seem to be thinking up as well
and so I wanted to make sure I came on
today even though I did not do it by 10
a.m. because I went to a cooperative
meeting I wanted to make sure that I did
in fact come on and do one and talk
about perfection and mental health just
because when it seems like the perfect
topic for today with bells let's talk
challenge I have been diagnosed with
anxiety and PTSD I also have ADHD and I
suspect some form of the autism spectrum
and learning how my brain works and how
it doesn't work and being kind to myself
has been a long path and I finally am
able to accept myself just the way I am
including having bad days and days where
I do feel like I can't make a video or
get out of bed and that wasn't yesterday
yesterday was a great day I just forgot
it just skipped my mind and those things
happen to me all the time - and just to
recommit to challenges and recommit to
the commitments I make instead of just
letting them all go away the irony is I
had four things I was doing it was
meditation I remember clay going yoga
and the video and the video is the only
one I managed to do every day I've
definitely been one or two days I've
missed meditation I think I've miss
klegg almost every day and there's only
been about half the days that I've done
yoga but it was something about because
I had continued to do the videos and
then did me time like now I failed at
all of them it's like no there's still
because I even meditated yesterday so
there still hasn't been a day
where I haven't done anything and so I
know from my experience I used to do
like everything started on the first and
I would do it for 30 days and it was
like an all or nothing and we have to
change like my entire diet and exercise
every day and it would always fall apart
as soon as it fell apart it fell apart
now I'm much more into okay let's
celebrate what you did do today and so
today I cleaned my bedding and I went to
a cooperative talk then had to crash for
two hours I'm taking my kid to her swim
lesson which I'm managing to get this
video done literally in the moments
before doing that and I'm proud of me
and everyone else who is potentially
struggling with mental issues physical
issues I don't even know what to say to
you except that you're perfect just the
way you are exactly as you are and
including when you need help and getting
help and when you're don't even know how
to get help and being in that state is a
big reason why I'm doing what I'm doing
and starting the cooperative because I
know how hard it can be to reach out and
the easier we make it for people the
easier we make it for people to find
community and information on every topic
the more did I'm hoping that they find
it easier to get help I know I would
find it easier in that situation to get
help so it's a video for today I'm gonna
go take my kids swimming and I will be
back tomorrow hopefully with a better
internet connection bye